<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Venn Tracker</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Venn Tracker</string>
    <string name="PREF_FILE">APP_PREF_FILE</string>
    <string name="HOME_LATITUDE">39.9542083</string>
    <string name="HOME_LONGITUDE">-75.1653137</string>
    <string name="First_Time">
        "Venn Tracker is an app meant to be used alongside Pokémon Go.
        \nTo learn how to use Venn Tracker, check out the Tutorials in the top left menu."
    </string>

    <!--Text for new features popup-->
    <string name="New_Features">
        "\n 1.25
        \n - Added import for json files
        \n - so far, I have only tested json exported from pokealert (contact me if you get any errors)
        \n - json filename must include "spawn"
        \n - Fixed error where it wasn't skipping spawn points that already exist
        \n\n1.24
        \n - Added import/export for spawn points.  Collaborate with friends or find data online.
        \n - Import and export are in BETA, please contact me with any bugs.
        \n - Exported data can be found in your downloads folder on your phone
        \n - Imported data must be in .csv format and must contain "spawn" in filename.
        \n - map overlay now refreshes less frequently
        \n\n1.23
        \n- The map long press menu now updates the overlay map when you add something
        \n- Map overlay is cleaner
        \n- Overlay should take up less system resources
        \n- Overlay map now updates every 2 seconds automatically (change in settings)
        \n- Overlay map now shows all spawn points if you don’t have any green area"
    </string>

    <!--Text for Circles tutorial-->
    <string name="Tutorials_Circles_1">
        "In Pokémon Go, your sighting\'s scanner\'s range is 200 meters.
        \n\nVenn Tracker allows you to make a visual representation of where a Pokemon on your sighting\'s list can be found."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Circles_2">
        "If you see a Pokémon on your sighting\'s list that you would like to catch, add a green circle.
        \nThis is the searchable area that it can be found"
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Circles_3">
        "The outside edge of the green circle indicates the 200 meter radius around your current location where Pokémon on your sighting\'s list can be found."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Circles_4">
        "If it is within 40 meters of you, it will spawn. Since it hasn\'t, we subtract that area."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Circles_5">
        "If it is still in your sighting\'s list after moving around, you can add another green circle.
        \nThe 2 shapes will be combined and you will only see where they intersect."
        </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Circles_6">
        "By just adding green circles, you can very quickly narrow in on it\'s location."
        </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Circles_7">
        "If it disappears off of your list, that means you have moved past 200 meters from it\'s location.
        \nSubtract a red circle to remove anything within 200 meters from you.
        \n\nTIP:
        \nIf your sighting's list is full, it may still be within the 200 meters but was just replaced on the list with something else.
        \nYou can catch some of the Pokémon you see while tracking in order to make sure the one you want has room on the list."
        </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Circles_8">
        "The searchable area will be greatly reduced.
        \nNow walk back to the green area and continue tracking :)"
        </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Circles_9">
        "When adding and subtracting circles, a lot of calculations are being performed on each point of each circle.
        \nIf the app is hanging when pushing the green/red buttons, try lowing the resolution of the circles in the settings menu."
    </string>

    <!--Text for Spawn Points tutorial-->
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Points_1">
        "In game, Pokémon will only spawn at specific locations on your map.
        \nVenn Tracker allows you to create spawn markers so you can map out the spawn locations near you.
        \nIf you have any spawn point markers within your searchable area, check there first.
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Points_2">
        "To create a spawn point marker, press and hold on the map where you want to add it until a dialog comes up to confirm."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Points_3">
        "Whenever you catch something in an area you play frequently, add a marker there so you know where to check in the future.
        \nThese markers are stored and loaded up each time you start Venn Tracker."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Points_4">
        "To delete a marker, just press it and hit 'Delete Marker'."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Points_5">
        "When tracking something, any marker outside of your searchable area will become transparent."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Points_6">
        "Adding and subtracting circles will also eliminate any spawn points outside of the searchable area."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Points_7">
        "Combining spawn points with circles while tracking will allow you to find what you are looking for very quickly."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Points_8">
        "<b>Tips:</b>
        \n\nSomething will spawn at a spawn point the same minute every hour.
        \n(There are some exceptions, but this is almost always true)
        \n\nEvery week or two, some spawn points get added and removed.
        \nSo far, most spawn points have been staying the same, but keep this in mind when tracking."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Times_1">
        "Pokémon will spawn at the same minute every hour and stay on the map for 30 minutes.
        \nVennTracker allows you to set the spawn time of each spawn marker.
        \nIf a time is set, you can see if that spawn point will have a Pokémon at it."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Times_2">
        "Blue markers indicate that you have not set a time for that marker.
        \nRed marker = Inactive, no Pokémon.
        \nGreen marker = Active, there will be a Pokémon."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Times_3">
        "To set a spawn time for a marker, touch it and select 'Spawn Time'."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Times_4">
        \n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n"Now select the minute that the Pokémon spawns."
    </string>
    <string name="Tutorials_Spawn_Times_5">
        "VennTracker will check each marker every 30 seconds to see if it has become active.
        \nWhen tracking a Pokémon, only check the spawn points that are indicated as being active."
    </string>


</resources>
